let savollar11 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "anymore",
        answer: "A. ortiq",
        options: [
            "A. ortiq",
            "B. hanuzgacha",
            "C. yana bir marta",
            "D. ko'proq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "asleep",
        answer: "B. uxlayotgan",
        options: [
            "A. uyg'oq",
            "B. uxlayotgan",
            "C. charchagan",
            "D. dam olgan"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "berry",
        answer: "A. malina",
        options: [
            "A. malina",
            "B. yong'oq",
            "C. olma",
            "D. gul"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "to collect",
        answer: "C. to'plamoq",
        options: [
            "A. yo'qotmoq",
            "B. tarqatmoq",
            "C. to'plamoq",
            "D. sotib olmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "to compete",
        answer: "D. musobaqalashmoq",
        options: [
            "A. hamkorlik qilmoq",
            "B. yordam bermoq",
            "C. taslim bo'lmoq",
            "D. musobaqalashmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "conversation",
        answer: "A. suhbat",
        options: [
            "A. suhbat",
            "B. monolog",
            "C. muhokama",
            "D. ma'ruza"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "creature",
        answer: "C. mavjudot",
        options: [
            "A. o'simlik",
            "B. bino",
            "C. mavjudot",
            "D. mashina"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "decision",
        answer: "B. qaror",
        options: [
            "A. shubha",
            "B. qaror",
            "C. imkoniyat",
            "D. afsus"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "either",
        answer: "D. yo",
        options: [
            "A. na",
            "B. ham",
            "C. kabi",
            "D. yo"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "forest",
        answer: "A. o'rmon",
        options: [
            "A. o'rmon",
            "B. sahro",
            "C. okean",
            "D. shahar"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "ground",
        answer: "B. yer",
        options: [
            "A. osmon",
            "B. yer",
            "C. tog'",
            "D. suv"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "to introduce",
        answer: "A. tanishtirmoq",
        options: [
            "A. tanishtirmoq",
            "B. yashirmoq",
            "C. xayrlashmoq",
            "D. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "to marry",
        answer: "C. turmush qurmoq",
        options: [
            "A. ajrashmoq",
            "B. sevmoq",
            "C. turmush qurmoq",
            "D. uchrashmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "to prepare",
        answer: "B. tayyorlamoq",
        options: [
            "A. unutmoq",
            "B. tayyorlamoq",
            "C. kechiktirmoq",
            "D. rad etmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "to sail",
        answer: "A. qayiqda suzmoq",
        options: [
            "A. qayiqda suzmoq",
            "B. uchmoq",
            "C. haydamoq",
            "D. cho'milmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "serious",
        answer: "C. jiddiy",
        options: [
            "A. kulgili",
            "B. do'stona",
            "C. jiddiy",
            "D. xavfsiz"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "to spend",
        answer: "D. o'tkazmoq",
        options: [
            "A. tejamoq",
            "B. topmoq",
            "C. yo'qotmoq",
            "D. o'tkazmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "strange",
        answer: "B. g'alati",
        options: [
            "A. oddiy",
            "B. g'alati",
            "C. odatiy",
            "D. an'anaviy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "truth",
        answer: "A. haqiqat",
        options: [
            "A. haqiqat",
            "B. yolg'on",
            "C. mish-mish",
            "D. fantastika"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "to wake",
        answer: "C. uyg'onmoq",
        options: [
            "A. uxlamoq",
            "B. tush ko'rmoq",
            "C. uyg'onmoq",
            "D. dam olmoq"
        ]
    }
];
